Birgit make it do it makes it welcome to
比尔吉特（Birgit）做到这一点，使其受到欢迎
the session on migrating to modules my
关于迁移到模块的会议
name is Mark Reynolds I work on Java one
我叫Mark Reynolds我从事Java开发
of the things how many people saw the
有多少人看到了
session I did yesterday afternoon Oh
我昨天下午做了会议哦
excellent that'll give you a head start
优秀，可以让您领先
I don't that will definitely help so
我不是一定会帮上忙
just like yesterday this is going to be
就像昨天一样
entirely live coding I probably will
我可能会完全编码
make a couple of mistakes if you spot a
如果发现一个错误，就会犯几个错误
mistake feel free to shout it out I
错误随时大声说出来我
don't mind being corrected if you have
如果有的话不要介意纠正
questions of clarification feel free to
澄清问题随时可以
shout those out too and I'll and I'll
大声喊那些，我会，我会
try to answer but real you know meat
尝试回答，但真正的你知道肉
it's meaty substantive questions let's
这是实质性的实质性问题，让我们
let's just leave those to the end ok so
让我们把那些留到最后好吧
what I've got here just as yesterday is
我昨天到这里来的是
a very fresh build of JDK 9 just just a
一个非常新的JDK 9版本，只是
few days old what we're going to do in
几天前，我们将要做什么
this session is is take a little class
这节课是上一堂课
path application that uses some popular
使用一些流行的路径应用程序
libraries and we're going to modularize
库，我们将进行模块化
it now those libraries themselves
现在那些图书馆自己
haven't yet been modularized in fact
实际上还没有模块化
they're a little old or not the latest
他们有些旧或不是最新的
version of those libraries so we'll see
这些库的版本，所以我们将看到
that you can modularize an application
您可以模块化应用程序
even though some of the libraries it
即使有些图书馆
uses have not yet been converted to
用途尚未转换为
modules then we'll do the reverse we'll
模块，然后我们做相反的事情
pretend that we're the maintainer z' of
假装我们是z的维护者
those libraries we'll modularize those
这些库，我们将对它们进行模块化
and see how our little application just
看看我们的小应用程序如何
sitting on its own on the class path can
独自坐在课堂上可以
make use of those now modularized
利用现在模块化的
libraries in an effective way and then
有效的方法，然后
finally at the end we'll have a
最终在最后，我们将有一个
beautiful module graph where
漂亮的模块图在哪里
everything's a module and the class path
一切都是模块和类路径
is empty which after all is the
是空的，毕竟是
long-term goal all right so I've got
长期目标没事，所以我有
here a file of tweets
这是一条推文文件
in JSON format of the century not
不是本世纪的JSON格式
particularly readable but hey it's
特别可读，但是嘿
better than exid nominee
胜过被提名人
so these are some tweets from my
这些是我的一些推文
timeline from a while back and what I
一段时间后的时间表和我
what I've written is a tiny little app
我写的是一个小小的应用程序
that will display these in a much more
将会在更多的地方显示这些
readable format so let's take a look
可读的格式，让我们看一下
we've got a main class pretty
我们有一个漂亮的主班
straightforward package or got tweets um
简单的包装或收到推文
that we're using the Jackson data
我们正在使用杰克逊数据
binding API so we import some classes
绑定API，因此我们导入了一些类
from that our main class is pretty
从这一点来说，我们的主要班级很漂亮
straightforward
直截了当
but we we configure a Jackson object
但是我们配置了一个Jackson对象
mapper to disable some projects disable
禁用某些项目的映射器
one of its properties we read this value
它的属性之一，我们读取此值
in from from the standard input stream
来自标准输入流
make make ourselves a list of tweets and
使自己成为推文列表，
then for each tweet in that list we just
然后针对该列表中的每条推文
run a little lambda to display it on on
运行一点lambda以将其显示在
the standard output stream and this this
标准输出流和这个
tweet class this is the other class in
鸣叫类这是另一个类
this tiny little application is
这个小小的应用程序是
basically just a little PO Java it's a
基本上只是一点点PO Java
data holder for a tweet pretty
推文漂亮的数据持有人
straightforward it's using the the
很简单，它使用
sequel timestamp class just for
续集时间戳类，仅用于
amusement import some jackson
娱乐导入一些杰克逊
annotations and then it's it's a pretty
注释，这是一个漂亮的
straightforward photo it's got it's got
简单明了的照片
two properties a text which is just a
两个属性是一个文本
string the body of the tweet and a
将推文的正文和
timestamp property which has the jackson
具有杰克逊的时间戳属性
annotations on it and that's the time
上面有注释
the tweet was posted of course there's
这条推文当然被发布了
lots of other information in a tweet but
一条推文中有很多其他信息，但
we're just trying to display the
我们只是试图显示
essential content so we don't care about
基本内容，所以我们不在乎
the rest and that's fine okay so let's
其余的都很好，所以让我们
compile i'm just let's just make sure
编译我只是让我们确保
this this all works is a regular old
这一切都正常了
class path application without it
没有它的类路径应用程序
without any anything special
没有什么特别的
i've got here
我到了
in my lib directory the Jackson jar
在我的lib目录中，Jackson jar
files 266 is a bit of a stale version I
文件266有点陈旧了
think the latest is 2.8 or something but
认为最新的是2.8左右
that's fine so let's compile Lib Jackson
很好，让我们编译Lib Jackson
annotations Lib Jackson clone and then
注释Lib Jackson克隆，然后
the lid Jackson data bind and let's see
盖杰克逊数据绑定，让我们看看
is that oh yeah let's do this really
是的，是的，让我们真正做到这一点
advanced thing here okay that should
这里先进的东西好吧，应该
compile everything yep let's make a mega
编译所有的东西，让我们做个大
jar
罐
let's see you let's just stick this in
让我们来看看，让我们坚持下去
lid
盖
OOP
面向对象
there's a dur file okay so I should now
有一个dur文件，所以我现在应该
be able to run this I'll just copy this
能够运行它，我将复制它
class path here
课堂路径在这里
ad-lib tweet some and/or tweet some
ad-lib鸣叫一些和/或鸣叫一些
named tweet stuff JSON
名为tweet的东西JSON
boom pretty display of some tweets okay
繁荣漂亮的一些推文显示还可以
so that was pretty straightforward we
所以这很简单
see we see that it works as it stands
看到我们看到它按原样工作
right so first part let's modular eyes
好的，所以第一部分让我们模块化的眼睛
the little tweet some application
小推特一些应用程序
without doing anything to the Jackson
不用对杰克逊做任何事
jar files
jar文件
we're just going to we're not going to
我们只是去，我们不会去
modify them we're just going to use them
修改它们，我们将要使用它们
as they as they exist so in tweet sound
因为它们的存在，所以在鸣叫声中
we'd to make this into a module what do
我们要把它变成一个模块做什么
we need exactly so let's make one of
我们需要，所以让我们做一个
those as you will recall module info
您将回忆起的模块信息
goes in the root of your package
进入包的根目录
hierarchy for the module and I need to
模块的层次结构，我需要
say well I need to give the module a
说的好，我需要给模块一个
name we'll just call it tweets um even
名称，我们甚至都将其称为推文
though that's not a very good name I'll
虽然那不是一个好名字
come back to that later what are the
稍后再说
essential things about a module it
关于模块的基本内容
requires ended exports let's talk about
需要终止出口让我们谈谈
exports first is tweets um need to
出口至上是推文um需要
export anything no it's an application
导出任何东西不，这是一个应用程序
that's not providing an API for anybody
没有为任何人提供API
else to use so we don't need any exports
其他使用，所以我们不需要任何出口
okay requires what do we type for
好吧，我们需要输入什么
required what do we require here so we
需要我们在这里需要什么，所以我们
know that tweets um uses those three
知道推文um使用了这三个
jacks and jar files so would it be nice
千斤顶和jar文件，所以会很好
if we could just type this or something
如果我们可以输入此内容或其他内容
like this but wait a minute these are
像这样，等一下，这些是
just jar files I'm these these are old
只是jar文件，我这些都是旧的
jar files off of central there they
他们从中央那里的jar文件
don't have any module infos in them
没有任何模块信息
right
对
meta and bunch of classes usual stuff
元和一堆班通常的东西
they're not modules
他们不是模块
so what do we do well it turns out we
所以我们做得好，结果证明我们
actually can type requires Jackson core
其实可以打字需要杰克逊核心
and that we can do that because of this
由于这个原因，我们可以做到这一点
feature called automatic modules so
功能称为自动模块，因此
automatic modules are a migration tool
自动模块是迁移工具
they let you take an existing jar file
他们让您获取现有的jar文件
you don't have to modify it you just put
您不必修改它，只需输入
it on the module path and the module
它在模块路径和模块上
system treats it as if it were a module
系统将其视为模块
it's a bit of a special module emetic
这有点特殊的模块催吐剂
and it has access to many more things
它可以访问更多的东西
than a regular module does but this is
比常规模块要多，但这是
essential for migrations okay so if you
对于迁移至关重要，所以如果您
haven't have some existing jar files
没有一些现有的jar文件
they're fairly well-formed they don't
他们的格式相当好，他们没有
have conflicting packages with packages
与软件包有冲突的软件包
any of that any of that kind of messy
任何那种凌乱的东西
stuff you just put them on the module
你把它们放在模块上的东西
path the model system synthesizes
模型系统综合的路径
declarations for them at compile-time
在编译时为其声明
and run-time and the name of a module is
和运行时，模块的名称是
taken from the name of its of its jar
取自其罐子的名称
file using a pretty simple heuristic in
使用一个非常简单的启发式文件
your Jackson dashboard 26.6 jar drop the
您的Jackson仪表板26.6罐子放下
extension drop the version part convert
扩展名删除版本部分转换
remaining punctuation to dots
其余标点符号
remove redundant dockets it's very
删除多余的码头，这是非常
straightforward it's not necessarily the
直接，不一定
best name for that module long term but
长期以来该模块的最佳名称，但
I'll discuss that more later on so I can
我将在以后再讨论，以便
say here in this module declaration for
在此模块声明中为
tweets um even though those Jackson jars
即使那些杰克逊罐子鸣叫
aren't proper modules I can say requires
我说的不是适当的模块
Jackson's Core requires Jackson data
杰克逊的核心需要杰克逊数据
bind and requires Jackson annotations
绑定并需要Jackson批注
okay now there's another way to figure
好吧，现在还有另一种方法
out what tweets um needs how many people
出来什么推特um需要多少人
know about the j-dub stool so gate up
知道j-dub凳子，所以登门
stool is a a tool that we we actually
凳子是我们实际上的一种工具
it's a tool to aid migration to aid in
这是帮助迁移的工具
the analysis of existing code it does a
分析现有代码，它会
static analysis of a jar file and can
对jar文件进行静态分析并可以
tell you lots of interesting things
告诉你很多有趣的事情
about its properties both as a potential
关于它的特性都具有潜力
module and in terms of what other
模块以及其他
modules it might need in order to run
运行可能需要的模块
this tool was it was so important that
这个工具是如此重要
even though
即使
development for nine we back ported it
九点开发，我们将其移植回去
to eight update releases so if you have
到八个更新版本，所以如果您有
a fairly recent build of JDK 8 then you
一个相当新的JDK 8版本，然后您
have the Jade ups tool it's not quite as
拥有玉器ups工具
modern as the one that's in 9 but it's
就像9中的那个一样现代，但是
there and you already got it you just
在那里，你已经知道了
might not know it so ok deficit among
可能不知道，所以好吧之间的赤字
other things a little side note as many
其他事情一点点注意
people know by now one of the things
人们现在知道其中一件事
that we've done in in Java 9 is
我们在Java 9中所做的是
encapsulate internal API so Jade EPS has
封装内部API，因此Jade EPS具有
the ability to tell you whether you've
告诉你是否有能力的能力
got a jar file that's using internal
有一个正在使用内部的jar文件
api's ok good tweet some does not using
api的好推文，其中一些未使用
general API if it had then done this
通用API（如果已执行此操作）
with this would have printed warnings
这样做会打印警告
and so forth alright but we can also
等等，但是我们也可以
just ask it for a summary of what does
只是问一下它做什么的总结
tweets um depend upon so it needs Java
um依赖，因此需要Java
dot base it needs Java dot sequel oh
点库需要Java点续集哦
right I forgot remember I use the
对，我忘记了我使用了
timestamp class so I better put that in
时间戳记类，所以我最好把它放在
hires gamma dot sequel because the
雇用了伽玛点续集，因为
sequel types are not in the base module
续集类型不在基本模块中
and then it's set here of what's this
然后在这里设置这是什么
not found stuff well but not not found
找不到好东西，但找不到
stuff is because I didn't tell it about
东西是因为我没有讲
the class path where all the Jackson
上所有杰克逊的课堂路径
things are let me grab a class path
事情让我抢了上课的路
give-give jaidev's a class path and then
给贾德耶夫的课程路径，然后
ask it to do the same analysis see now
要求它做同样的分析
it now determines that tweets um is
现在确定推文um是
using types in those three jackson jar
在这三个杰克逊罐中使用类型
files
档案
all right so I've got I've got a modular
好的，我已经有了模块化
eyes tweets um let's compile bad now
眼睛鸣叫嗯，让我们现在编译不好
Java C has gotten pretty clever about
Java C变得非常聪明
compiling models compiling modules is a
编译模型编译模块是一个
fairly different thing than compiles
与编译完全不同的东西
compiling a bunch of files for the for
为编译一堆文件
the classes directory and sticking those
classes目录并将其粘贴
in a jar file so Java C is pretty clever
在jar文件中，因此Java C非常聪明
now we're going to put the output in in
现在我们将输出放入
mods we're going to tell it the module
mods，我们将告诉它模块
path is the Lib directory and let me
路径是Lib目录，让我
just remove that old tweet send a jar
只需删除旧的推文发送一个罐子
file from the Lib directory for now ok
Lib目录中的文件现在确定
we need so the module path is it's kind
我们需要这样的模块路径是一种
of like the class path but it's
就像上课的路，但是
important in some different ways it's
在某些方面很重要
where the system finds modules at
系统在哪里找到模块的地方
compile time and at runtime one of the
编译时和运行时之一
essential differences from a class path
与课堂道路的本质区别
is once a module is found there classes
一旦找到模块
in that module are only loaded from that
该模块中仅从该模块加载
modules jar file it doesn't do the
模块的jar文件不会执行
stupid naive thing of searching every
愚蠢的天真搜寻
jar file on the class path from front to
从前到后的类路径上的jar文件
back and taking the first class in that
回到那边上头等舱
package that it happens to find a big
碰巧找到一个大包装
part of reliable configuration okay so
可靠配置的一部分好吗
to compile we also can give it a module
编译我们也可以给它一个模块
source path and that's just our source
源路径，这只是我们的源
directory until it what module we want
目录，直到它是我们想要的模块
to compile and Java C will go off and
进行编译，Java C将会消失，
look at it we'll go find all those files
看看它，我们将找到所有这些文件
do time to time stamp comparison and
做时间戳比较
figure out what needs to be compiled and
弄清楚需要编译什么，
there we go whoops mmm now this worked
在那里，我们走了
earlier they Oh
他们早些哦
yeah well what's my error I put them on
是的，我把它们放在我身上的错误是什么
to Limbo in the wrong directory
到错误目录中的Limbo
okay let's compile it again tada
好吧，让我们再次编译它
okay so we've got an exploded an
好吧，我们已经爆炸了
exploded form of the tweet some module
推特模块的分解形式
in the Mazda rectory we can now we can
在马自达直肠，我们现在可以
we can do a lot lots of things let's
我们可以做很多事情，让我们
let's run Java P on at module in focus
让我们在焦点模块上运行Java P
to make sure it looks right there enough
确保它看起来足够正确
yet it's pretty much what I typed
但这几乎是我输入的
earlier good and like we can now make a
早先的好，就像我们现在可以做一个
jar file we'll put this back in Lib
jar文件，我们将其放回Lib中
tweet some jar
鸣叫一些罐子
right
对
was quits in there the dark chill has
在那阴暗的寒冷中退出了
also been enhanced it knows quite a bit
也得到了增强，它知道很多
about modules we can for example say
关于模块，我们可以说
describe module and it will go find the
描述模块，它将找到
module info if there is one and tell you
模块信息（如果有）告诉你
about its content okay so we've got the
关于它的内容还可以，所以我们有了
the Lib directory
Lib目录
tweet-tweet some jar is a proper module
鸣叫一些罐子是一个适当的模块
the Jackson jars are unchanged they will
杰克逊罐子将保持不变
be used as automatic modules now I
现在用作自动模块
should be able to run us give the
应该能够运行我们给
runtime my module path that's just the
运行我的模块路径
Lib directory I want to run the tweet
我要运行推文的lib目录
some module I need to tell it what what
我需要告诉一些模块什么
the main class is although I could have
主要的课是虽然我可以
defined that actually but I just didn't
定义了实际上，但我没有
and let's read read the tweets a JSON
让我们读读推文的JSON
file whoops now that didn't work did it
现在文件没用了
hmm what happened so what happened here
嗯，发生了什么，所以这里发生了什么
is we've got an inaccessible object
是我们有一个无法访问的对象
excited exception unable to make or
无法做出激动的异常或
delete some tweet accessible the
删除一些可访问的推文
constructor because module tweets um
构造函数，因为模块鸣叫um
does not open or done tweets um to
没有打开或完成推文
module Jackson data bind what's going on
模块Jackson数据绑定发生了什么
here so Jackson data bind isn't it isn't
在这里，杰克逊数据绑定不是，不是
it is a small example of a framework
这是一个框架的小例子
that uses reflection it's when one of
使用反射是当其中之一
these reflective frameworks now because
这些反思性框架现在是因为
a big thing a big theme of this entire
一件大事，整个主题
effort has been providing strong
努力一直提供强大
encapsulation so the module system by
封装使模块系统通过
default encapsulate s-- api's in in
默认封装s-- api位于
packages they're not accessible at
软件包，它们在以下位置不可访问
runtime you need to you need to export
您需要导出的运行时
them where you somehow make them
他们你以某种方式使他们
available if that's what you need so
如果您需要的话可以使用
let's go back to the module info in the
让我们回到中的模块信息
proper directory what we might try is to
适当的目录，我们可能尝试的是
say that this exports
说这个出口
read on tweet some right just going to
在推特上阅读一些正确的只是去
work
工作
okay well let's sign out
好吧，让我们退出
all right I'm going to I'm going to save
好吧，我要去保存
some time here by using a little shell
在这里用一个小贝壳
script that I have that combines with
我拥有的脚本
the Java C in the jar steps into one
jar中的Java C融入其中
I'll drill path Lib module source source
我将钻探路径Lib模块的源代码
okay goes off and compiles makes a jar
好了，编译成一个罐子
file and let's run that again what's
文件，让我们再次运行它是什么
going to happen it still doesn't work
将会发生，但仍然无法正常工作
why doesn't it work
为什么不起作用
here we go the sane and accessible
在这里，我们理智而方便
object object exception the reason it
对象对象异常的原因
doesn't work is that simply exporting a
不起作用的是，仅导出一个
package does not make it available for
软件包无法用于
the kind of deep intrusive reflection
一种深层的侵入反射
that many of these reflective frameworks
许多这样的反思框架
require that is also intentional if
要求也是故意的
you're defining an API you want you want
您正在定义想要的API
to be able to say okay I'm exporting
可以说好，我正在导出
some some interfaces and some classes
一些接口和一些类
for use by other modules you know it's
供其他模块使用，您知道
certainly it's fine for them to
对他们来说当然很好
reference them in the normal way at
以正常方式引用它们
compile time reference them in a normal
编译时以正常方式引用它们
way at runtime but since I want to
在运行时的方式，但由于我想
protect my internals you know imagine
保护你的内心，你知道
we're talking about the java dot base
我们在谈论Java点库
module we're protecting the internals is
我们保护内部的模块是
essential for security and integrity
对安全性和完整性至关重要
deep reflection should not be allowed by
不应允许深度反射
default so there's another keyword we
默认，所以还有另一个关键字
can use and that is called opens as was
可以使用，这就是所谓的打开
suggested in this error message so
在此错误消息中建议
instead of typing exports here I'll say
而不是在这里输入导出，我会说
that this module opens the tweet some
该模块打开了鸣叫一些
package one and what that means is this
打包一个，这是什么意思
package is not available at compile time
软件包在编译时不可用
a compile time it's a it's not an API
它不是API的编译时间
but it is available at runtime for deep
但它在运行时可用于深度
reflection I'm the owner of this code I
反射我是此代码的所有者
know I'm using a reflector framework I
知道我正在使用反射器框架
don't mind if that reflected your
不要介意这是否反映了您的
framework pokes deep into the internals
框架深入内部
of that package that's okay that's
那个包装的没关系
actually my intent now it is possible if
实际上，我的意图是现在
you really need to you can you can both
你真的需要你可以
open and X
开和X
or a package the actual need for that
或包装的实际需要
seems to be pretty rare but you can do
似乎很少见，但是你可以做
that another thing an alternative we
那另一件事是我们的替代品
could do is we get open the entire
可以做的是我们打开整个
module and that would make every package
模块，这将使每个包
be open and sometimes that's a way to
开放，有时这是一种方法
save some typing but it's no different
保存一些打字但没什么不同
than saying opens of every package
而不是说每个包裹都打开
that's there so we'll just do this full
在那里，所以我们会做完整的
opens or got tweets um will recompile it
打开或收到推文um将重新编译它
and we'll run it and there now we have
我们将运行它，现在我们有了
the tweet some application it's a module
推特一些应用程序是一个模块
it's using the Jackson jar files as
它使用杰克逊的jar文件作为
automatic modules and it's all working
自动模块，一切正常
all right what's next let's make a make
好的接下来做什么
a little Jerry with the J link tool so
一点Jerry和J链接工具
that we can take a closer look at what's
我们可以仔细看看是什么
actually going on here I've got a little
其实在这里我有一点
make file here's a little Jerry doesn't
制作文件，这里有点杰里没有
have much in it but it has everything
里面有很多东西，但是它拥有一切
that we need we know we needed sequel we
我们需要我们知道我们需要续集
always need base and sequel it turns out
总是需要基础和续集
pulls in logging and XML just well
很好地记录日志和XML
because XML ok so we can now rerun rerun
因为XML没问题，所以我们现在可以重新运行
this with a little reduced Jerry and
这与减少杰里和
yeah it works not only does it work but
是的，它不仅有效，而且
there's there couple of new options in
那里有几个新的选择
the runtime want to show module
运行时要显示模块
resolution this has changed from
分辨率从
previous versions we did a big cleanup
以前的版本，我们做了很大的清理
recently on on all the command line
最近在所有命令行上
options so if you show module resolution
选项，如果您显示模块分辨率
then the runtime will print as it goes
然后运行时将进行打印
essentially a progress report of what's
本质上是进度报告
going on as it configures the module
在配置模块时继续进行
system so you can see at the top it
系统，因此您可以在顶部看到它
starts with the root module is tweets um
从根模块开始是推文
the module that we're starting with
我们开始的模块
that's what the thing we're trying to
这就是我们要尝试的事情
run tweets um requires got some data
运行推文um需要一些数据
bind have got a sequel injection
绑定有续集注射
annotations the messages show you where
消息的注释显示您在哪里
those modules are defined in most case
这些模块在大多数情况下都已定义
it's in a file but Java dot sequel he
它在文件中，但是Java点续集他
has this funny URL Jay arty :
有这个有趣的网址Jay arty：
Javadoc sequel that means it's a it's a
Javadoc续集，这意味着它是一个
module built into the system image using
使用以下命令内置到系统映像中的模块
using the internal jrt virtual file
使用内部jrt虚拟文件
system and then and then it builds the
系统，然后再构建
rest and we're off to the races okay so
休息，我们要去比赛了，所以
a word about automatic modules they've
关于他们拥有的自动模块的一句话
been a bit controversial it's been
一直有争议
difficult to to find just the right way
很难找到正确的方法
of sort of threading our way through
穿过我们的方式
through the various trade-offs if what
通过各种取舍，如果
you have is an application and it's not
你有一个应用程序，但不是
something it's not something where
有些东西不在哪里
you're going to be publishing it's not
您将要发布它不是
something it has an API and you're not
它有一个API的东西，而你却没有
going to be publishing it for for
将要发布
external use then automatic modules are
外部使用，那么自动模块是
a great tool that enable you to get
一个伟大的工具，使您能够
started modularizing your applications
开始模块化您的应用程序
if you've got an internal application
如果您有内部应用程序
maybe it's actually composed of a bunch
也许实际上是一堆
of modules you can you can you can do
可以的模块数量
that or you can start with a big
那或者你可以从一个大的开始
application that isn't and decompose it
不是的应用程序并将其分解
into modules it's it's perfectly fine
放入模块中就可以了
for those modules to use existing jar
让那些模块使用现有的jar
files as automatic modules what's not
文件作为自动模块是什么
such a good idea is if you're the
这样的好主意是
maintainer of a library especially its
图书馆的维护者，尤其是图书馆的维护者
popular if you're the maintainer of a
如果您是
library that you publish to maven
您发布到Maven的库
central or wherever and that and you
中央或任何地方，那与你
modularize it and make that library
模块化并制作该库
depend on other jar files using their
依靠其他jar文件使用它们
automatic module names that's a bit
自动模块名称有点
risky because I essentially when when
冒险，因为我基本上什么时候
those windows jar files you're using as
您正在使用的那些Windows jar文件
automatic modules are eventually
自动模块最终
modularized hopefully by their
他们希望将其模块化
maintainer z' they might choose a
维护者z'，他们可能会选择一个
different name
别的名字
in fact hopefully they'll choose a
事实上，希望他们会选择
sensible reverse DNS module lane which
明智的反向DNS模块通道
long-term is the best way to name a
长期是命名一个的最佳方法
module rather than the funky one that we
模块，而不是我们的时髦
derived from the Arctic from from the
源自北极
jar file name essentially the maven
jar文件名本质上是Maven
artifact ID so so to sum up if your
文物ID，因此，如果您的
modularizing code that's that's internal
这是内部的模块化代码
to your organization using automatic
自动使用您的组织
modules is fine be prepared that as
模块准备好了
those jar files are modularized you
这些jar文件是模块化的
have to adjust your module declarations
必须调整您的模块声明
because their names could very well
因为他们的名字很好
change but if you're maintaining a
变化，但如果您要维护
library that is published for external
为外部发布的库
use upon central or wherever you publish
在中央或您发布的任何地方使用
it be very wary of publishing a module
发布模块非常谨慎
that depends on automatic modules
取决于自动模块
because you're essentially putting users
因为您实际上是在吸引用户
of your module at risk of things
您模块的风险
breaking later on and not the way for
后来打破而不是
you to update yours okay so we've mod
你更新你的好吧，所以我们已经
flairies tweets um let's go the other
天才推特，嗯，我们去其他
way around well that's interesting the
很好的方式有趣
time left says it's still 50 minutes
剩下的时间说仍然是50分钟
when I'm flying blind here okay no
当我在这里盲目飞行时，可以
worries I'm going to clean things up
担心我要收拾东西
here I'm going to move forward and we're
在这里，我要前进，我们
now in a different world
现在在另一个世界
so here's tears tweets um I'm going to
所以这是我的眼泪鸣叫
compile this the same same way that I
编译方式与我相同
that I did before it's going to be a
我之前要做的是
plain ol jar file no mado time left 27
普通ol jar文件没有剩余时间剩余27
minutes thank you okay I'm going to
分钟，谢谢，好吧，我要去
compile this in the normal way and I'm
以正常方式编译它，我
going to cheat and just say web slash
要作弊，只说斜线
star
星
okay so I've got tweets um jar and
好吧，所以我有推特和罐子
there's no module info in there it's
那里没有模块信息
it's a plain old jar file now let's
这是一个普通的旧jar文件，现在让我们
pretend that we are the maintainer of
假装我们是……的维护者
the Jackson JSON libraries as it happens
Jackson JSON库的发生
I have source code for those three jar
我有这三个罐子的源代码
files that we've been using here and
我们一直在这里使用的文件
they they're they're not modules yet but
他们是他们还不是模块，但是
we can look inside and see ya comm
我们可以看看里面，看到你的通讯
faster XML Jackson core a bunch of
更快的XML Jackson核心
classes you know all those other stuff
你知道其他所有课程
met in services whatever so so that's
在服务中相遇，所以这是
all there how do we go about making a
所有在那里，我们如何去做一个
module declaration for the Jackson core
Jackson核心的模块声明
artifact the jackson core project well
神器杰克逊核心项目很好
we can run jaidev's that'll give us some
我们可以运行jaidev，它可以给我们一些
idea right this will tell us about the
正确的想法，这将告诉我们有关
requires just as it told us about the
就像它告诉我们有关
requires we would need we would need for
要求我们需要
for tweets on itself we can we conceal
对于自身的推文，我们可以隐藏
this information so that really helps us
这些信息确实对我们有帮助
with the requires but not with the
与要求，但与
exports what do we do about that well we
出口我们如何做得好
could do something kind of crude we
可以做些粗暴的事情
could look at say the directory
可以看一下目录
structure of that and say okay well yeah
的结构，然后说好吧
they're going to be packages
他们将成为包裹
corresponding to to all these things but
对应于所有这些东西，但是
that would be well kind of tedious so J
那会很乏味，所以J
depths to the rescue again
再次进行救援
Jade EPS has yet another option whereby
Jade EPS还有另一种选择
we can ask it to generate module in
我们可以要求它生成模块
Python Java files j-dub generates module
Python Java文件j-dub生成模块
info and I'm going to type the stool is
信息，我要输入凳子是
going to write write code into my source
将写代码写入我的源代码
tree always a little dangerous so be
树总是有点危险，所以要
careful that you actually want to do
小心您实际上想做的
that Lib Jackson core and now I've got a
Lib Jackson的核心，现在我有一个
module info let's pop back into Emacs
模块信息让我们回到Emacs
here
这里
there's the module info generated by
有由生成的模块信息
Jepsen well actually that looks pretty
吉普森实际上看起来不错
good it exports the packages exports all
好，它出口包装出口全部
the packages by default there's a new
默认情况下，有一个新的
thing here and that is that there's this
这里的东西就是那个
provides clause so
提供条款
side note the module system knows about
侧面说明模块系统知道
services if you're familiar with Java
您熟悉Java的服务
util service loader that's been around
util服务加载器已经存在
for a long time it's a it's a
很长一段时间是
straightforward service provider
直接的服务提供商
facility that's been in the platform
平台中已有的设施
we've upgraded that so it's it's
我们已经升级了，就是这样
integrated with the module system the
与模块系统集成
module system understands services the
模块系统了解服务
module system needs to understand
模块系统需要了解
services because if you have a service
服务，因为如果您有服务
provider it might require some
提供者，可能需要一些
additional modules and so if it's all
其他模块，如果是全部的话
part of the whole the whole resolution
整个决议的一部分
and configuration process and so what
和配置过程等等
this statement is saying is that the
这句话是说
Jackson core module provides this
Jackson核心模块提供了此功能
Jackson this Jason factory service and
杰克逊这杰森工厂服务和
it figured that out by reading the meta
它通过阅读元知道
and slash services directory okay end of
和斜杠服务目录可以
side note all right let's compile the
旁注好吧，让我们编译
jackson core module now that we have it
现在我们有了杰克逊核心模块
i'm going to put these these new modules
我将把这些新模块
in a different directory called
在另一个目录中
em lib
图书馆
and there we go jar described and that's
然后我们去描述罐子，那是
exactly what we expect so let's let's go
正是我们所期望的，所以让我们开始吧
on and do the Jackson annotations and
然后做杰克逊注解和
data bind jar files and what I'll do is
数据绑定jar文件，我要做的是
I'll just run a EPS on everything here
我将对这里的所有内容运行EPS
so it's going to generate three module
所以它将生成三个模块
infos now when you when you use Jade
当您使用Jade时立即显示相关信息
apps to do this it's always a good idea
应用程序这样做总是一个好主意
to go look at what it created because
去看看它创造了什么，因为
what it created might not make any sense
它创造的东西可能没有任何意义
or it could perhaps be improved so
也许可以改善一下
here's the data bind model it's quite
这是数据绑定模型
quite a large module let's let's take a
相当大的模块，让我们来
look for first of the exports are there
寻找那里的第一个出口
any exports here that look like they
这里的任何出口看起来像他们
don't belong or maybe a bad idea to
不属于或者不是一个好主意
export hmm you till now maybe it but
出口你直到现在也许吧，但是
that it will not be not being expert in
不会不是专家
the internals of this of this project
这个项目的内部
I'm not not sure but there are
我不确定但有
definitely these implies sitting around
肯定这些意味着坐着
and you kind of suspect well if a
如果您有怀疑的话
package is named dimple and yeah don't
包名为dimple，是的，不要
export it so let's not do that okay so
导出它，让我们不要那样做吧
we won't export those or look there's
我们不会导出这些内容，也不会看到
another service provider and then back
另一个服务提供商，然后返回
at the top this is this is worth noting
在顶部，这是值得注意的
these are requires directives but
这些是要求指令，但
they're a special kind of requires
他们是一种特殊的要求
directive as Erik they're called
被称为Erik的指令
requires transitive what does this mean
需要传递是什么意思
well it's essentially establishing a
好吧，这实际上是建立一个
one-step transitive transitive shortcut
一步式传递式快捷键
so the Jackson data bind module exports
所以Jackson数据绑定模块导出了
all of these packages those packages
所有这些软件包
include classes and interfaces whose
包括其类和接口
signatures refer to types in the Jackson
签名是指杰克逊中的类型
annotations module the Jackson core
批注模块Jackson核心
module that got a sequel module in the
模块中有续集模块的模块
java xml module so some other modules
java xml模块以及其他一些模块
say tweet some that's using the jackson
说鸣叫一些使用杰克逊的东西
data binds module it it doesn't need to
数据绑定模块，它不需要
say that it also requires jackson
说这也需要杰克逊
annotations
注解
courses and Java Seagal in XML because
课程和XML中的Java Seagal，因为
that's given to it by these requires
这些要求赋予了它
transitive direct directives and an
传递直接指令和
informal sense you can think of it
你可以想到的非正式的感觉
requires transitive as saying not only
不仅需要传递和说
this this module require that one but
这个模块要求
this module re-exports the API of that
该模块重新导出该API
one to any modules that use this module
一个到任何使用此模块的模块
so it technically it's not really react
所以从技术上讲它不是真的反应
sports what it what it really is is it's
运动它的真正含义是
saying that the user module also
说用户模块也
requires the that module but react sport
需要那个模块但是反应运动
is is a good informal way to think about
是一种很好的非正式思考方式
it okay so that's the data bind module
好的，那是数据绑定模块
right
对
okay so let's compile data bind well
好吧，让我们编译数据绑定好
annotations first and then we'll compile
批注，然后我们将进行编译
data bind
数据绑定
that's kind of a big module takes a
这是一个很大的模块
little bit and now we've got our three
一点，现在我们有三个
Jackson modules in the end Lib directory
Lib目录末尾的Jackson模块
okay I already took
好吧，我已经拿了
let me move tweets um out of out of that
让我将推文从中移出
regulars of Lib directory and just put
Lib目录的常客，只是把
it here so we're sure we're not using
它在这里，所以我们确定我们没有使用
the original versions of Jackson or
杰克逊的原始版本或
anything anything weird like that okay
像这样的任何奇怪的事
let's try to run this now Java module
让我们尝试现在运行此Java模块
path M Lib CP classes because that's
路径M Lib CP类，因为那是
where well actions CP tweed summed up
CP花呢总结得好
jar or got tweets um main from tweets up
jar或从tweets上获取tumets um main
Jason hmm Oh what happened no class
杰森嗯发生了什么事没课
death found error comp ass for XML
死亡发现XML的错误补偿
Jackson core blah blah blah is not there
杰克逊核心等等等等等等不存在
well what happened is the Jackson
杰克逊发生了什么
modules there on the module path but
模块在模块路径上，但是
they weren't loaded they weren't
他们没有被加载
resolved the reason they weren't
解决了他们不是这样的原因
resolved is tweets and AH jars just just
解决的是推文和AH罐只是
a regular old jar file there's no module
常规的旧jar文件，没有模块
stuff going on here there's no way for
这里发生的事情没有办法
the runtime system to figure out the
运行时系统找出
tweets an actually needs those so I
推特实际上需要那些，所以我
actually have to tell it with another
其实不得不告诉另一个
option add modules Jackson core Jackson
选项添加模块Jackson核心Jackson
data bind Jackson annotations and now it
数据绑定杰克逊注释，现在
works so we had to do a little bit of
工作，所以我们不得不做一点
manual configuration because tweets um
手动配置，因为鸣叫um
is just sitting there off in the
只是坐在那里
classpath as an optimization if your if
类路径作为优化，如果您
you remembered this since Jackson data
你记得杰克逊的数据
bind requires Jackson core injects and
绑定需要杰克逊核心注入和
annotations we can actually get away
我们实际上可以摆脱的注释
with something shorter here we are
还有一些较短的东西
actually only need to mention Jackson
其实只需要提杰克逊
data vine so not not quite as much
数据藤所以不是那么多
typing is required so you might be
必须输入文字，因此您可能会
wondering how does the class path relate
想知道类路径如何关联
to modules well in in the model system
在模型系统中很好地进行模块化
the way we've we've set things up every
我们已经设定的方式
class every type is actually in a module
类，每种类型实际上都在模块中
but there is a special module called the
但是有一个特殊的模块叫做
unnamed module just as we have had
未命名的模块
basically from the beginning of time
基本上从时间开始
there's a notion of the unnamed package
有一个未命名包的概念
in Java if you just type you know foo
在Java中，如果您只是键入就知道foo
Java and it's not in any package you can
Java，它不在任何包中
write you can write that you can compile
写你可以写你可以编译
you can run integrate it it's in
您可以运行它集成在
technically incorrect to say it's not in
从技术上讲它不在
any package it actually is in a package
实际在包装中的任何包装
it's called the unnamed package and if
它被称为未命名包，如果
you read the fine print and the Java
您阅读了精美的文字和Java
language specification the java vm spec
语言规范Java vm规范
you'll see how this is how this is all
您会看到这是怎么回事
worked out so we've done a similar trick
解决了，所以我们做了类似的技巧
here in the module system code in the
在模块系统代码中
classpath is load into into the unnamed
将classpath加载到未命名的文件中
module it's a module that has no name
模块是没有名称的模块
the unnamed module reads it infected
未命名的模块读取它被感染
requires every other module that was
需要其他所有模块
already resolved and so that's how we
已经解决了，这就是我们的方式
that's what we make sense of things it
这就是我们对事物的理解
also of course exports everything
当然也出口一切
because well that's exactly what the
因为那正是
class patent does so did I make it
类专利是我做到的
yellow let's make that little diagnostic
黄色让我们做出一点诊断
Jerry again
杰瑞再次
and we can run run it on that little JRE
我们可以在那个小的JRE上运行它
and let's do the show modules as we go
让我们边做展示模块
and you can see here that it's doing
你可以在这里看到它正在做
pretty much what we expect that the add
我们几乎期望增加
modules option on the command line
命令行上的modules选项
[Music]
[音乐]
specified additional routes for
指定的其他路线
resolution but it configured the Jackson
分辨率，但它配置了杰克逊
they Devine modules configure the rest
他们由Devine模块配置其余部分
and then and then off we win okay so
然后我们就赢了，所以
that's modularizing the libraries
模块化的库
without modularizing the application
无需模块化应用程序
just to finish up let's go back and make
最后，让我们回去做
tweets um into a proper module again
再次将um推到适当的模块
requires exome data blind
需要外显子组数据盲目
that look right I think that's right
看起来不错，我认为是正确的
okay to compile that
可以编译
module path and live tweet some tweets
模块路径和实时鸣叫一些鸣叫
time JSON good and here's the diagnostic
时间JSON好，这是诊断
we start with tweets um we see tweets um
我们以推文开始，我们以推文开始
requires some things and we configure
需要一些东西，我们进行配置
Jackson data vines and the rest of it
杰克逊数据藤和其他
and we're done we have a nice simple
我们完成了一个很好的简单
module graph the class path is empty
模块图类路径为空
everything is running as a module so to
一切都作为模块运行，因此
sum up migrating to modules does take
总结迁移到模块确实需要
some work it's possible to do it without
一些工作，没有它就可以做到
waiting for all the libraries that you
等待着你所有的图书馆
use to migrate to modules and that's
用于迁移到模块，那就是
okay this is a sent in a way this is a
好吧，这是发送方式，这是一个
trick that we borrowed from generics if
如果从仿制药那里借来的技巧
remember remember when generics were
记得记得泛型是什么时候
introduced in Java 5 way back when we
当我们回到Java 5中时
left the notion of raw types in and we
保留原始类型的概念，我们
did not put in reified types which is it
没有输入修饰类型
remains a controversial decision but the
仍然是一个有争议的决定，但
reason for that was exactly to allow you
原因恰恰是为了让你
to genera fie your own code without
无需创建自己的代码
waiting for all the libraries did you
等待所有的图书馆你
use to be genera fide and that's worked
过去通常是诚实的，这是可行的
out pretty well although there's still a
很好，尽管仍然有
distressing amount of code out there
令人苦恼的代码量在那里
that has not yet been genera fide but
还不是真正的，但是
there it is so this is a trick that's
就是这样，这是一个把戏
come to be called migration
被称为迁移
compatibility and automatic modules are
兼容性和自动模块是
way to get migration compatibility as
获得迁移兼容性的方法
hopefully everyone moves over time
希望每个人随着时间的流逝
towards towards modules something that's
朝向模块的东西
something to say about that it's it's
可以说的是
not a I certainly don't expect every
不是，我当然不希望每一个
active body of code out there to migrate
活跃的代码主体在那里迁移
to modules migrating an existing large
迁移现有大型模块
body of code to modules can be extremely
模块的代码体可能非常极端
costly and painful I mean it took us
昂贵而痛苦的是我花了我们
what eight years to modularize the JDK
JDK模块化的八年时间
so my recommendation for an existing
所以我对现有的建议
system is think carefully before you
系统是您之前要仔细考虑的
start down the path of modular ization
开始模块化的道路
you know the OSGi folks are completely
你知道OSGi的人是完全
right about this modularizing an
关于这个模块化的
existing code base can be a ton of work
现有的代码库可能需要大量工作
and frankly it might not be worth it but
坦率地说，这可能不值得，但
if you're starting a new project from
如果您正在从中开始一个新项目
scratch then definitely consider using
从头开始然后绝对考虑使用
modules from the start okay
从头开始的模块
so further information jigsaw is has
所以进一步的信息拼图是
been remain remains a fairly big project
被保留仍然是一个相当大的项目
it's covered by six separate JDK
它由六个单独的JDK覆盖
enhancement proposals in the open JDK
开放的JDK中的增强建议
community plus jazz are 376 for the
社区加上爵士乐是376
module system itself and that's in the
模块系统本身，它位于
Java community process so this is part
Java社区流程，因此这是一部分
of JDK 9 it's it's there it's been in
JDK 9的存在
there for quite a while you can get you
在那里有一段时间你可以得到你
can get the latest JDK 9 early access
可以获得最新的JDK 9抢先体验
build that at JDK Java net / 9 that's a
在JDK Java net / 9上构建
new URL the old one redirects here but
新网址，旧网址重定向到这里，
that's up that's a new URL we've moved
这是我们移走的新网址
it because the rest of java.net is going
这是因为其余的java.net都在进行中
away so it's there when will this be
离开所以它会在那里
released mmm I don't know with with the
发布了我不知道的mmm
the drama earlier this week
这周早些时候的戏
I think the current schedule which has a
我认为目前的时间表
ga date of July 27 is probably a bit
ga日期为7月27日可能有点
unrealistic but I'm hopeful that we can
不切实际，但我希望我们能够
ship within a small number of months
几个月内发货
after that all right we've got 12
在那之后，我们有12
minutes for questions I work for Oracle
我为Oracle工作的问题分钟
don't believe a word I've said are there
不相信我说过的一句话
are the microphones there and Mike
那里的麦克风和迈克
go back to the info page
返回信息页面
when you took Java core and made it a
当您采用Java核心并使其成为
module and we compared the modular class
模块，我们比较了模块类
that you created by hand and then what
你手工创建的，然后是什么
was put into the module itself I thought
被认为是模块本身
I saw it had a requires java-based
我看到它有一个基于Java的需求
mandated I saw that however you remember
强制我看到，但是你记得
the exact Oh in in the you saw the word
确切的哦，在你看到这个词
mandated probably in the describe module
可能在describe模块中授权
output yam right requires Java mandated
输出山药权需要Java强制
right so so that's that's a good
对，所以那是一个很好的
question Allah allow me to explain just
问题阿拉让我解释一下
the the described module option 2 the
所描述的模块选项2
jar command and similar things such as
jar命令和类似的东西，例如
when you run it you run Java P they they
当您运行它时，您将运行Java P
show you more than you can express in
向您展示超出您表达能力的内容
source code because they're they're more
源代码，因为它们更多
they're more bits in a class file then
他们是一个类文件中的更多位
then then then right strictly needed to
然后然后然后严格地需要
express what's in the source code one of
表示源代码中的内容之一
the bits in a class file is whether for
类文件中的位是否用于
requires directive that was mandated by
需要由
the Java language specification so it's
Java语言规范，因此
it's a it's a it's it's kind of it's
这是一个它是它的一种
it's in some ways of more theoretical
在某些方面更理论化
use than practical use but it tells it
使用比实际使用，但它告诉我们
can tell a tool for example that this
可以告诉一个工具，例如
requires directive was inserted by Java
Java插入了require指令
C because it's mandated by the spec
C，因为它是规范要求的
rather than rather than something that
而不是
was actually expressed in the code if I
如果我实际上在代码中表示
had typed requires Java dot base myself
自己输入需要Java点库
that mandated wouldn't be there so it's
该命令不会在那里，所以它是
it's a subtle distinction but it's abuse
这是一个微妙的区别，但它是滥用
to some kinds of tools
某些工具
put in the front
放在前面
and in this sample I saw that you opened
在这个样本中，我看到您打开了
they put some mod module but this is a
他们放了一些模组，但这是一个
simple case right so you have they put
简单的案例吧，所以你把他们放
some application module and it's really
一些应用程序模块，实际上
simple but what happens if you have
很简单，但是如果有
something some properties in there like
那里的一些属性像
a automatic decimal or a class from
自动小数或
another module of our class from another
我们班上另一个模块
package that another library that is not
打包另一个不是的库
with modularized how do you how do you
与模块化你如何
manage that sorry let me make sure I
对不起，让我确保我
understand the question because oh wait
了解问题，因为哦，等等
wait what if tweetIn had been using even
等待，如果tweetIn一直在使用
more complicated types from some other
其他一些更复杂的类型
module because Jackson now is just
模块，因为杰克逊现在只是
trying to get the properties from the
试图从中获取属性
twits for each class Brian that's easy
每个班级都推特，布莱恩很简单
right and you're hoping that to be able
对，你希望能够
to access but what happens if you have
访问，但是如果您有
more and properties in that class that
以及该类中的更多属性
are not open okay so so what if there
还没开好怎么办
are additional Kojo properties in the
的其他Kojo属性
tweet class that use types that are in
使用以下类型的推文类
that are defined in the tweets and
在推文中定义的
module but not open another module or in
模块，但不能打开另一个模块或在
another module another not oh yeah it
另一个模块另一个不，是的
actually doesn't matter where they are
其实不管他们在哪里
then well it'll it'll depend on exactly
那好吧，这完全取决于
how how the Jackson data bind framework
Jackson数据如何绑定框架
how deeply it needs to go it may be that
它需要走多深可能是
it only needs to do reflection on on the
它只需要对
tweet objective objects themselves right
推文客观对象本身正确
and and if and if the value of one of
并且，如果且如果其中之一的值
those properties is you know some other
这些属性是你知道其他一些
type somewhere else as long as it's
只要在其他地方输入
exported and Jackson can use its public
出口，杰克逊可以使用其公共场所
API and that'll be fine but if Jackson
API，那很好，但是如果Jackson
for some reason has to begin then that
由于某种原因必须开始
that other type this thing is for this
其他类型的东西是为此
value will also have to be in a package
值也必须放在包装中
that's open for reflection but usually
这是值得反思的，但通常
in this in these reflective framework
在这些反思框架中
committed they don't tend to follow
承诺他们不会跟随
object graphs in that way
这样的对象图
so they'll manipulate what you tell them
所以他们会操纵你告诉他们的
to manipulate and everything else they
操纵和其他一切
just treat as a fake types
只是当作假的类型
so my question is about the early
所以我的问题是关于早期
runtime failures I guess that we've
运行时失败，我想我们已经
introduced so the runtime now catches
引入，因此运行时现在可以捕获
some class of errors placed on package
包装上存在一些错误
names in modules and so on
模块中的名称等等
yes right so if the library I use
是的，所以如果我使用的图书馆
evolves its API in a braking way by
通过制动方式改进其API
renaming a package that will be called
重命名将被调用的包
early on at runtime hmm if a library the
如果库在
library is evolved and it renames a
库不断发展，并将其重命名为
package that in general that will be
包装一般
fine but if that package now conflicts
很好，但是如果该软件包现在有冲突
with something else then that could be a
与其他东西，那可能是一个
problem in the runtime will detect it
运行时中的问题将检测到它
I guess my real question was if if the
我想我的真正问题是，如果
packages are still as they used to be
包仍然像以前一样
but the classes gets renamed is it
但是类被重命名了吗
detected early on or does it fail at the
尽早发现或失败
very last moment like you stated you can
最后一刻，就像你说的，你可以
rename classes little work fine you
重命名课程一点工作都没问题
might get a new class that founder later
可能会在以后开设一个新班级
on if you if you've got code here code
如果您有代码，请继续
that you didn't recompile like you
你没有像你一样重新编译
didn't edit recompile that's referring
没有编辑指的重新编译
to that but that's just the usual thing
但这只是平常的事情
the analysis done by the runtime the
运行时进行的分析
yupo sorry the additional analysis that
yupo对不起，补充分析认为
does now is limited to the module graph
现在只限于模块图
and the package structure of each module
以及每个模块的包装结构
it does not look more any more deeply
它看起来不再更深
than that it doesn't go and look at
比它不去看
types and say that oh well this this
输入并说哦，这个很好
class is now referring to something that
班级现在所指的是
doesn't exist that's detected in the in
在中检测到的不存在
the same old way no class def to founder
同样的方式，没有创始人的阶级定义
when the code gets there that's not
当代码到达那里时
detected up front
预先检测到
thank you
谢谢
my question is about versions very
我的问题是关于版本的
meaning of the modules
模块的含义
what about sorry versioning so a virtual
不好意思的版本控制呢
different versions of one module how
一个模块的不同版本如何
colors is countably I didn't see any in
颜色可数我没看到任何
the module in for any mentioning about
关于模块的任何提及
version is there any concept of that or
版本是否有该概念或
not the number one frequently asked
不是经常问的第一名
question there there are not versions in
问题那里没有版本
this module system this all has also
这个模块系统也都有
been in some quarters a controversial
在某些方面引起争议
design decision there are not versions
设计决定没有版本
in this model system it does not attempt
在此模型系统中，它不会尝试
to solve the the multiple versions
解决多个版本
problem whatever that means it has
问题是什么意思
several different meanings because if it
几种不同的含义，因为如果
did then you probably wouldn't like the
那样的话你可能会不喜欢
result and there are two main reasons
结果，主要有两个原因
why you probably wouldn't like the
为什么你可能不喜欢
result
结果
one is that the behavior of many
一是许多行为
existing api's that have anything to do
现有的api可以做什么
with class voters even indirectly will
与选民甚至间接
change in incompatible ways so it makes
以不兼容的方式进行更改，因此
the process of moving to modules more
移至模块的过程更多
difficult perhaps bigger reason you
困难也许是更大的原因
might not like the result is that all of
可能不喜欢结果是
the popular build tools have no idea
流行的构建工具不知道
what it means to solve the multiple
解决多重问题意味着什么
version problem you look at maven Gradle
你看Maven Gradle的版本问题
all of these tools they go out of their
所有这些工具，他们都走了
way to detect conflicts and point them
检测冲突并指出冲突的方法
out and this is why conflict resolution
出来，这就是为什么要解决冲突
can be such a pain in the butt during
可能会在屁股上如此痛苦
development but it's something you have
发展，但这是你所拥有的
to do because ultimately on you know on
之所以这样做，是因为最终您对
the class path today you version have
今天版本的课程路径
two versions of the same thing are
同一件事的两个版本是
almost always a recipe for disaster now
现在几乎总是灾难的根源
long term yeah it would be great to
从长远来看，
solve the multiple version problem it
解决多版本问题
would be great to have some way of you
拥有某种方式会很棒
know but module a means version 1 of
知道但模块的意思是版本1
module B and module C needs version 2 of
模块B和模块C需要版本2
module B and as long as we can guarantee
模块B，只要我们可以保证
that the types from those two versions
那两个版本的类型
of B will never intersect and meet
的B永远不会相交和相遇
because that would like you know caused
因为那你想知道造成了
an implosion then then we could support
内爆然后我们可以支持
that we have the plumbing for all of
我们有所有的管道
that now you know it is it is something
现在你知道它是什么
that we could do with not an enormous
我们可以做的不是很大
effort but a but not a trivial one
努力，但不是一件小事
either in the future release but doing
在将来的版本中
it now would lead to
现在它将导致
a less than satisfactory experience
不太令人满意的经历
because the tools don't support it and
因为这些工具不支持
it will take it'll take a while it would
这将需要一段时间
take take a while for them to do so it's
花一些时间让他们这样做
been you know it's it's taken long
你知道这花了很长时间吗
enough to get the tools you know just to
足以获得您知道的工具
support what we've done so far you know
支持我们到目前为止所做的一切，您知道
if we if we decided to solve the
如果我们决定解决
multiple version problem
多版本问题
we could do that it would take another
我们可以做到，这将需要另一个
you know months year I'm not sure how
你知道一年的时间我不确定
long for the tools to catch up so what
渴望工具赶上，所以
we've got is a good foundation I think
我认为我们有一个很好的基础
it's best to get this out now what
最好现在就把它弄清楚
people start modularizing and we'll take
人们开始模块化，我们将采取
a deep look at the multiple version
深入了解多种版本
problem for future release which as I
我将来发布的问题
said yesterday might be sooner than you
说昨天可能比你早
think but what they've one module like
想想，但是他们有一个像什么的模块
generally acquired like available module
通常像可用模块一样获得
Megan reporter or something has changed
梅根记者或有什么变化
API between versions and one dependent
版本和一个依赖项之间的API
module is using one version the other
模块正在使用一个版本
ones using the other version which one
使用其他版本的
will be used as what I'm saying that the
将被用作我所说的
comment all right right right right
评论好吧好吧好吧好吧
right now you right now you're just
现在，你现在，你只是
stuff that you just have to pick one
你只需要选一个的东西
you know you what you what you do today
你知道你今天做什么
to resolve conflicts in maven or Gradle
解决Maven或Gradle中的冲突
or ivory or whatever tool you're using
或象牙或您使用的任何工具
you can you can you'll continue to do
你可以，你可以继续做
that right you know the mob the mob the
没错，你知道暴民
semantics of the module path are the
模块路径的语义是
module system starts at the front it
模块系统从它的最前面开始
looks in each directory for a module of
在每个目录中查找以下模块
the name that it's looking for it takes
它要寻找的名称
the first one that it's find and then
找到的第一个，然后
from that point point that point on
从那个点到那个点
that's the definition of the module of
那是模块的定义
that name in there it never looks again
那里的名字再也不会出现
okay okay two minutes one last question
好的，好的，两分钟，最后一个问题
I'm imagining I'm working in a spring or
我在想我在春天工作还是
Java environment and would I then
Java环境，然后我会
usually open my application for
通常打开我的申请
reflection completely because it's so
完全是因为反思
common like for hibernate for spring
常见，如春季冬眠
whatever oh yeah
哦，是的
so it opening your whole application
这样就打开了整个应用程序
completely sure you could do that for a
完全确定您可以做到这一点
start but but in general if you're using
开始，但一般来说，如果您使用
you know spring hibernate any of any of
你知道春天冬眠的任何
these reflective frameworks it's it's
这些反射性框架
it's best to think a little bit as your
最好把你的想法
modular eyes well which of your packages
模块化的眼睛很好，您的包装
are actually going to beam that be
实际上是要发出光束
manipulated by spring or hibernate or
被春季或冬眠所操纵，或
whatever and and just open those I mean
随便打开我的意思
if you want to you can just make make
如果你愿意，你可以做
your whole module open and and and
您的整个模块打开，并且和
that'll work but as a as a general point
那会起作用，但作为一个普遍点
of hygiene opening just the packages
卫生只打开包装
that need to be opened is a better
需要打开是更好的
practice but as a library developer I
练习，但作为图书馆开发人员
will not know if my library might be
不知道我的图书馆可能是
used in the reflective frame bug as art
在反光镜框虫中用作艺术品
so that that's it that's a good question
就是这样，这是一个好问题
it turns out there's there's a there's a
原来那里有一个
small and subtle feature that will that
小而微妙的功能
will actually enable that for reflector
实际上将启用反射器
frameworks even though your thing is not
框架，即使你没有
open and I don't have time to explain
开放，我没有时间解释
its details right now so I think you
现在它的细节，所以我想你
yeah it's the I believe we have that
是的，我相信我们有
case covered okay times up thank you
案件涵盖好时间了，谢谢
very much I will be on hanging around
我非常会在周围闲逛
the rest of the day sometimes at the
剩下的时间有时在
Oracle booth sometimes in sessions so if
Oracle展位有时会在会议中出现，因此如果
you have further questions feel free to
您还有其他问题，请随时
to grabbing all right thank you
抓住好吧谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]